<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<root>
  <stories>
    <storie no="68" feature="true" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing this holiday!</header>
      <headline>Mary Christmas Goes To Planet X-MS20</headline>
      <content>
        While cleaning out her garage, Mary finds a portal, which leads to a forgotten world of quiet winter. What adventures wil she have there? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="67" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Rick Boogers And The SpaceGoats</headline>
      <content>
        In a universe of infinite complexity, one can onle speculate as to what kind of business Rick Boogers had with the SpaceGoats! Tune in for this weeks episode!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="66" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing this summer!</header>
      <headline>The NeverMind aka The Universal Mind</headline>
      <content>
        It was a mind of such unfathomable magnitude it could understand any problem in any conceivable reality. But would it ever be able to understand the intricate workings of human behaviour? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="65" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in theaters now!</header>
      <headline>Joe Oblivious And His Yodeling Moonboat, A Musical</headline>
      <content>
        Powered by the HyperX Yodl Engine, Joe travels between the distant stars in the sky. Whereever he arrives he tells of the many very lengthy adventures, he has had in his Moonboat. Tune in for more stories like this!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="64" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in cinemas now!</header>
      <headline>The Bomb Of Tomorrow</headline>
      <content>
        By inventing the S-Bomb, Dr. Dummkopf had mastered the science of stupidity. Now his only objective was.. WORLD DOMINATION! Tune in if you dare!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="63" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>OnionMan vs. OpinionMan</headline>
      <content>
        One was made up of layers, the other had made up his mind. Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="62" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>AtomsMan</headline>
      <content>
        He is made up by mostly atoms and the occasional doughnut. He fights for the little things and protects Earth against his nemesis Capt. NuClear. Dare you Watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="61" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>BrainHackers From Space (v2.0)</headline>
      <content>
        They came from a more advanced version of space, to hack our minds! But will General Consensus be able to stop them? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="60" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>The Fiend With Many Names</headline>
      <content>
        Some call him Malgamak, others Malgomak, Malgamok or Malgomok. But to his friend he is just Ollie. Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="59" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Love Stories From Dimension Zero</headline>
      <content>
        His name was Dot, her name was Dottie and together they were singular. Tune in for an evening of ROMANCE!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="58" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Adventures Of A Stocastic Neural Generator</headline>
      <content>
        Having been employed by the department of calculations for nearly a decade, CALC.ON_v2.0 a sentient calculator, goes through a mild midlife crisis ans finds it the right time to try out new things. Join him on his exotic explorations on THE INTERLINK!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="57" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in theaters now!</header>
      <headline>Brainless Monsters From Deep Space</headline>
      <content>
        They seek the braingod "Brainiac", collector of minds, because something was stolen from them and now they want it back? Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="56" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Order Of The Control Patrol</headline>
      <content>
        A group of middle aged men tries to enslave the people of Earth with piles of paperwork and bureaucracy. Now it's up to Betty Bizzaro to bring back a little chaos and make the world wear pants again! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="55" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon..</header>
      <headline>Getting Easy With RelaxoMan</headline>
      <content>
        From the comfort of his home, RelaxoMan would sit and watch the news and eat snacks, while commenting the law enforcement on the things he would have done differently. Tune in to follow the adventures of this comfortable avenger!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="54" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing!</header>
      <headline>General Consensus And Mr. McNeato, A Documentary</headline>
      <content>
        This week we will meet two men with many differrences, but can they both agree that they are a couple of fine gentlemen? Tune in to learn more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="53" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>BrainScans From Planet Brainus</headline>
      <content>
        All the way from across the galaxy comes the BrainScans. But will the good Dr. Membrain be able to understand all these medical terms in time? Tune in, if you dare!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="52" feature="false" love="false" top="true">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Adventures Of Future-Girl</headline>
      <content>
        We are set in a faraway future, where all events have already passed. All that is left is the future! Introducing the new girl wonder, Future-Girl!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="51" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Wrath Of The Fonigugus</headline>
      <content>
        They have unlimited wrath for no good reason, but also they like to goof around and watch bad sitcoms on a friday night! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="50" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>The Untold Storie Of The Incredible Wo-Man</headline>
      <content>
        From behind the curtins, he/she would make his/her puppet of a man (or woman), make inappropiate gestures and burst ludacris comments, to confuse his (or her) opponents! Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="49" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Interlink</headline>
      <content>
        Digital Drugs, they were the craze of the new age. In a blink of an eye, you will wake up having spend several hours on "The Interlink". Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="48" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing this summer!</header>
      <headline>Claire Voyant Gets A Brainjob</headline>
      <content>
        She had always envied the other girls for their bigger brains, so she goes to see Dr. Membrain to get brainimplants. Now she can do both long division and cook at the same time! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="47" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Scoofies Goes To Hollywood</headline>
      <content>
        Glamour! Glitter! Fame! Their only shortcoming, a craving for the sweet limelight of Hollywood. Tune in for an evening of music and dance galore!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="46" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>Invasion Of The Love-Machines</headline>
      <content>
        They came from Planet Love, vibrating their way into the hearts of the good people of Earth. How many, How often, noone really knows. Tune in for an evening in good company!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="45" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>The Bearded Man And The Cirque d'Freaks</headline>
      <content>
        His traveling circus hosted some of the most spectacular acts and misfits. But he himself never found anything special about his beard. Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
  
  
  
  
    <storie no="44" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Come on, Man! Strikes Again</headline>
      <content>
        He was the lesser known brother of YesMan. Using his powers to point out wrongs around the globe! Tune in for an evening of ACTION and ADVENTURE!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="43" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this Summer!</header>
      <headline>Prof. Galacto finds the hidden..</headline>
      <content>
        He had spend his life searching long and wide for it. But as he had almost given up, it appeared before him. Tune in to find out if this will be the next new thing in Intergalactic Space Travel!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="42" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Mr. McNeato Goes To The FriendZone</headline>
      <content>
        On his way through the galaxy, Mr. McNeato ventures a region of space called "The FriendZone". But what kind of dangers might he encounter here? Join Mr. McNeato on his fantastic voyage through space!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="41" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing this summer!</header>
      <headline>Jerry And The Mindsurfers</headline>
      <content>
        They spend their vacation surfing the greatest minds, listening to hip music and basking in the sun. But in the other end of town the Speed Freaks of Quadrant 5 are up to something! Tune in for an evening of action and intrigue!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="40" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>Frank Montgomery vs. Life</headline>
      <content>
        Frank was a normal man, paying his taxes, going to work. But one day Life invades and everything is about to change. Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="39" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Hidden Invasion Of The Scoofies</headline>
      <content>
        Undetectable to the untrained eye, one might be disguised as your neighbors new coffee table, another as a national television broardcast. Their numbers: Unknown. Their mission: To make lives comfortable throughout the galaxy. Tune in if you dare!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="38" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>Gunlar, Gundar or.. Both?</headline>
      <content>
        One a technological wonder, the other a master of bureaucracy. But which is which and what was their purpose. Tune in if you Dare!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="37" feature="false" love="false" top="true">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Alt Raum</headline>
      <content>
        It was a room containing all of the known universe, located at the end of the hall, 2nd door to the right. Join Mr. McNeato as he ventures the paths of this strange and mysterious place, The Alt Raum!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="36" feature="false" love="false" top="true">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Agenda Of The Free Will Society</headline>
      <content>
        Under strict guidance of the 'Free Will Amendment Act, Article 13'. A group of few select people sought to bring about their secret agenda! Will they succeed? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="35" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>The Terrorizing Horror</headline>
      <content>
        Vulgarity! Horror! Shock! It's like looking at yourself in the mirror in the morning after a night out, only more terrifying! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="34" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Playing at a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>AstroMan meets Mrs. Claire Voyant</headline>
      <content>
        In his relentless persuit for justice, AstroMan meets Claire Voyant, a seer of sights. Together they form a mighty team and fight side by side against the Evil Tentacles of The Past! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Claire Voyant And The Land Of Everton, Liverpool</headline>
      <content>
        It was a land of pure imagination, located so deep in the minds of the 7 guardians of the world, that only a true seer would be able to find it! Follow Claire Voyant on her journey to the land of magic and imagination!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="32" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinama near you!</header>
      <headline>Max Velocity And The Speed Freaks Of Quadrant 5</headline>
      <content>
        Max Velocity, leader of the gang at Galactic High and Hank, leader of the Speed Freaks both wanted the same girl. So they arrange a race to Keplars Bow and back. But who will win the heart of OctoGirl, a cheerleader from the planet Squid-Nation. Tune in for an evening of excitement, action an romance!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="31" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>Space Slugs From The Stratosphere</headline>
      <content>
        Terror! Horror! Excitement! They travel from deep space to slime your front porch! Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="30" feature="false" love="false" top="true">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Sir Real And The 8th Dimension</headline>
      <content>
        In order to escape the trivial matters of everyday life, Sir Real Builds The Matter Displacement Devise. A Devise which shifts trivial matter to the 8th dimension. Tune in to learn more about Sir Real and his incredible devise!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="29" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>The Time Traveller</headline>
      <content>
        He travels from the present into the future at the speed of regular time! Tune in to follow the adventures of The Time Traveller!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="28" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>SmartBots From Virturon.Beta.5</headline>
      <content>
        They are great at keeping a clean desktop, but when it comes to keeping a conversation going, any Gundar in the galaxy would rather have the company of a toaster! Tune in to find out more about the social and political landscape of Virturon.Beta.5!
      </content>
    </storie>
  
  
  
  
  
    <storie no="27" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Brain-Bugs From OUTER Space</headline>
      <content>
        From the farthest region of outer space and into your personal space, comes the Brain-Bugs. The reason for this.. to simply mess up your good mood! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="26" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon to a cinama near you!</header>
      <headline>Ray Gunn And The Love Nymphs</headline>
      <content>
        They had a craving for love, but all he could give them, was two smoking guns! Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="25" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Dr. Membrain And His Incredible Mind Machine, A Christmas Storie</headline>
      <content>
        He wanted it to help him invent a new machine of mass destruction, but it had a will of its own and only wanted to hear Wham and get in the holiday mood. Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="24" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Capt. Nuclear vs. The Cult Of Freedom Hippies</headline>
      <content>
        They wanted to save the trees, he wanted a nuclear powerplant. A mighty battle was fought, but in the end they settle and make a new home on Mars.. The End!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="23" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Mysteries From Beyond The Universe</headline>
      <content>
        Learn how creatures from the Planet Nonsensus made sense of it all, using only a pensil sharpener, a flat hat and some duct tape!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="22" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Day Aether-Monkeys Ruled The Earth</headline>
      <content>
        They soared through the airwaves and into the minds of the people of Earth. Now it was up to Genaral Consensus to stop them! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="21" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Mr. McNeato And The Planet Of A Thousand Dreams</headline>
      <content>
        He took a week of work to explore the galaxy. But in his wildest dreams he would never have imagined, what he was about to experience. Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="20" feature="false" love="false" top="true">
      <header>Now playing!</header>
      <headline>The Dreammachine</headline>
      <content>
        It was all nuts and bolts, but beautiful dreams were made! Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="19" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Coming to a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Splendid Ways Of Mr. Starman McNeato</headline>
      <content>
        He was a nifty gentleman and had a magnetic character. But what dangers would he meet on his romantic space endevours? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="18" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>They Came From The Planet Brainus</headline>
      <content>
        They worship the Brain-God, Brainiac. They use their brain for evil, but will their brainwaves enslave the good people of Earth, dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="17" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon..</header>
      <headline>The President From Another World</headline>
      <content>
        There is a crisis on Earth, so will words like "covfefe" and "China" be enough to save the world? Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="16" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing this summer..</header>
      <headline>Explores Of The 8th Dimension</headline>
      <content>
        They found a portal to another world but what will they find on the other side?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="15" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>The Brain Zombies From Venus</headline>
      <content>
        They came from a distant world to suck our brains and drink lattes at fancy cafes! Now it's up to General Consensus to stop them, but will he succeed in time? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="14" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>The Adventures Of Ray Gunn, Intergalatic Space Bandit</headline>
      <content>
        In this weeks episode, Ray bedazzles the women of Kau-W, robs a spaceport casino and saves a Gunlar from falling into a wormhole! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="13" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>A Romance In OUTER Space</headline>
      <content>
        They thought it was love, but creatures from deep space made them change their minds!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="12" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming this summer!</header>
      <headline>Tentacles From The Past</headline>
      <content>
        They reach across time and into your life, Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="11" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>The Brain Of The Future</headline>
      <content>
        Will it survive the struggles of daily life in our time?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="10" feature="false" love="true" top="false">
      <header>Now playing at a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>Mr. McNeato And The Fembots</headline>
      <content>
        Although a crafty ladies man, Mr. Starman McNeato stood no chance against these robots of love! Tune in to find out what happens next!
      </content>
    </storie>
  
  
  
  
  
  
    <storie no="9" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a theater near you..</header>
      <headline>Invasion OF The Baby Terrorists</headline>
      <content>
        They poop and barf their way into your hearts. Tune in this summer to watch!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="8" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Army Of The Mecha-Men</headline>
      <content>
        They were build for war, but in their internal combustion engines there was a longing for pease! Tune in to find out more!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="7" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>FutureMan, A Man Of Tomorrow</headline>
      <content>
        He fights crime tomorrow, so we can have better lives today. Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="6" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming Soon!</header>
      <headline>Brain-Suckers From Uranus</headline>
      <content>
        They travel across the galaxy to suck your brain! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="5" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing!</header>
      <headline>The Amasing Man With No Brain</headline>
      <content>
        He knew he would never be a rocket scientist. So he settled in the suburbs as an insurance salesman, where he provided well for his family and their dog. In his later years he would become an avid stamp collector and an active member at the local senior citizen carecenter! Dare you watch?
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="4" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a theater near you!</header>
      <headline>Dr. Membrain And His Amasing Automaton</headline>
      <content>
        He had finally completed building his fully functional automaton. But was it a weapon of mass destruction or a neat household appliance? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="3" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Now playing in a cinema near you!</header>
      <headline>Dr. Membrain And The Eather Monkeys</headline>
      <content>
        Sometimes he wondered, how his cybernetically enhanced super monkeys, would always manage to get drunk from the laboratorium eather. Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="2" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Coming soon!</header>
      <headline>He-Man, Master Of The Universe</headline>
      <content>
        He is blond, wears tight shorts and wrestles an evil foe, Skeletor. But does he have the power, tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
    <storie no="" feature="false" love="false" top="false">
      <header>Playing now!</header>
      <headline>The Search For The Missing Brain</headline>
      <content>
        They had looked everywhere! In the kitchen, on the table, behind the couch, but it was nowhere to be found! Will they find it in time? Tune in to find out!
      </content>
    </storie>
  </stories>
</root>